Thank you for choosing ICICI Credential
Life Insurance as your trusted life
insurance partner. Let's get to know
more about fund switch which is a unique
feature of your unit linked insurance
plan.
This feature helps you manage your ULIP
investments effectively. Let's
understand the benefits of this feature.
One, tax-free. Switch funds taxfree.
Two, long-term wealth creation.
Built for long-term goals, ULIPS let you
adjust your investment strategy as per
your risk appetite. Here's how you can
switch your funds in a few easy steps.
Visit our website www.iciprolife.com.
Click on login and select individual.
Enter your credentials or login using
login via OTP option. Once logged in,
click on transactions from the menu.
Select switch and click on transfer
funds.
Now select the policy for which you want
to switch funds. After selecting the
policy, the current fund details will be
displayed. Go to the from fund option
and select the fund that you wish to
switch. Now select a fund of your choice
and allocate a percentage to the new
fund selected. Click on add to proceed.
Review your total switch amount details.
Once you are done, click submit to
finalize your transaction.
You'll receive confirmation of the
transaction details via email and SMS.
You can also apply for the fund switch
option using our mobile app.
Log to our mobile app using your login
ID and password.
Click on all services. Select fund
switch under fund transactions.
Once selected, you'll be seamlessly
redirected to the website to complete
the process.
Use the switch fund today to invest in
the funds of your choice. Binder note.
[Music]